Elizabeth Valdez.
She's a loyalty tester.
Ana put me on a loyalty test.
Right now,
she thinks there's a woman involved.
But once she realizes that's not the case,
she'll become suspicious of other things.
Her coming here means
she knows something.
I can be surprising too.
I'll find a way to throw her off.
I need to catch them in the act
because that will be my proof
that he's cheating on me!
No! No! No! Liar!
Liar! Liar!
Go on. Do it.
And I'll tell Ben everything you did.
Problem solved. It's over.
I hope that's enough to get Ana to stop.
- Ana?
- Hmm?
Everyone knows and sees
how beautiful and talented you are.
But no one really knows
what you are to me.
You... are that ray of sunshine...
that led me out of my...
dead-end maze of a life.
You are proof...
that I deserve...
a good life.
And this is the beginning of my new life.
I found the love...
to live...
and kill for.
Because no one knows
what it really feels like
to be loved by you.
So, on this very lovely day...
...I give you my love eternal,
my loyalty,
and my life.
I love you more than my life, Ana.
I love you more than my life.
Ben,
I promise to be your safe space
when the world feels heavy.
To be your home
when things are uncertain.
To keep choosing you...
again and again
in every version of tomorrow.
I love you.
I now pronounce you man and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
Take two, please.
My husband's in tears.
One more time.
Beautiful.
Let me take that,
Nanny Cedes.
- Thank you very much.
- Okay, sir.
I got this.
I just want this to be perfect.
You're very sweet, sir.
Love?
Ana?
Ah, perfect! Just in time! I...
Ana, what's wrong?
Ana!
Ana?
That stupid woman!
She had the nerve to come here,
only to back down in the end!
My goodness.
The way she spoke to me, Diane!
You'd think I was the worst person alive!
Yet she's the one
who doesn't trust her husband,
to the point of putting him
on a loyalty test!
She did this to herself.
I asked her several times
if we should continue this.
She kept saying yes, again and again!
And now it's my fault?
That after being a loyalty tester
for so long,
I've fallen for Ben?
Yes, it's your fault. You fool!
What did you say?
Do you even hear yourself?
Are you seriously blaming Ana
for getting upset
when you flirted with her husband?
Tch. That's how it begins!
Flirting!
I don't care!
I love Ben.
So you really are crazy.
Didn't you say it was nothing?
You lied.
Then fine, call me a liar if you want!
This is how I feel!
Sure, you have feelings.
But for heaven's sake, stop it!
No matter how you look at it,
that fantasy of yours is going nowhere!
Ana.
Are you okay?
Ana, what's wrong?
Hey.
What's wrong?
Stop! Stop! Stop.
Ana, why?
Talk to me.
Ana, please talk to m--
Stop! I said stop!
Okay... please. Please... Ana.
Ana.
Ana, calm down.
You can talk to me. You can talk to me.
We can talk. We can talk, Ana.
Come on, talk to me.
Do you still love me?
Ana, I love you very much.
I love you. I love you so much.
- What's wrong?
- I saw you and Beth.
Where?
At the wharf.
I saw you!
I saw you with her!
- Ana! Ana! Calm down!
- I saw you with her!
I can explain this! I can explain this!
- I can explain this!
- Stop!
You just have to listen to me.
I can explain this.
Yes, I was at the wharf.
She was there too.
It's not what it seems.
I can explain this. Yes, I was--
- You were kissing! You were kissing!
- No, we--
What do you expect me to think?
- She kissed me!
- It's the same thing!
- No! I didn't kiss back!
- That's the same thing!
Please...
just listen to me, please.
- Just please.
- Just stop it.
Are you in a relationship with her?
No!
I am not in a relationship
with anyone else but you.
Ana, please just listen to me.
She's nothing to me, okay?
- She's nothing to me.
- No! You expect me...
to believe that? Huh?
It was just the two of you there!
Ana, I understand you.
But when I arrived,
she was already there.
- I swear--
- And the kiss?
- She kissed me all of a sudden!
- No, no, no!
Ana, she kissed me.
I don't know what she was thinking!
I was surprised!
Ana, I told her,
"What are you doing?"
I saw you!
I was there! I saw it!
Don't lie to me!
I know what I saw!
I love you so much.
I don't have any other relationships.
I even told her
that I was a married man!
- "What are you doing?"
- No, no!
I'm not stupid!
How could you do that to me?
How...
how could you do that to me?
Am I not enough?
You are.
You are enough.
What am I lacking?
Why did you do that to me?
Ana, nothing.
You made me look so stupid!
Don't touch me!
What is it that I'm lacking?
Nothing.
You're more than enough.
How could you do that to me?
Ana, you are perfect to me.
You're perfect, okay?
You are enough. You are more than enough.
You are more
than what I asked and wished for.
Ana, you're the love of my life.
I love you so much.
Only you.
There's no one else.
No...
- Ana, believe me.
- No!
- No...
- Ana, please.
- Stop! You're lying!
- There's no other woman!
- You're only good at lying!
- I'm not! No, I'm--
Ana, I'm not!
Ana.
Fuck!
You said you loved me.
Yes.
You said you love me more than your life.
I love you more than my life, Ana.
I love you for as long as I live.
Nothing has changed, Ana.
It's still the same.
Even more, Ana.
Ana, please let me explain.
I have nothing to do with this woman.
I don't know what she did.
She's crazy.
Then why...
why does it hurt like this?
Ana, please...
Ana, please talk to me. Come on.
Please open the door.
Let's talk about this.
I love you, Ana. You know that.
You know me better than this, Ana.
I will never lie to you.
I was gonna talk to you about it.
Ana.
Ana?
Nanny Cedes!
Where's the bathroom key?
Ben, please pick up.
Why won't he pick up?
"Ben, please pick up. We need to talk."
Nanny Cedes!
Sir!
- Here, Attorney.
- Ana, please open the door!
- Here are the keys.
- Just stay there!
- All right.
Stay right there.
Ana, please open the door!
No...
Can I come in?
I'm telling you, please...
Nothing happened, nothing happened.
No!
- Ana...
- Why?
Ana, Ana... don't do it.
Ana, please, don't hurt yourself.
Ana, don't do it.
Ana, look at me.
No, no, no! Ana, please, I'm begging you.
I'm begging you, please. No, no, no! Stop!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Ana, Ana!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Do it to me instead.
I can't live without you.
I'll take it instead.
Please, come on.
Please, please...
Let go, let go.
Let it go.
Okay, okay, okay...
Okay, let go.
It's okay...
It's okay.
- It's okay.
- No, don't touch me.
- Please, don't touch me.
- Okay, okay.
What do you need? Huh?
What do you need?
I just want to go to... Ma-Mama...
Okay, go.
Great, okay...
I love you.
No!
- Let me out of here!
- Regina!
- Let me out of here! I want to go out!
- Get me out of here!
- Regina!
- Please, get me out of here!
Stop that! What are you doing?
- You stop, Mara!
- Enough!
You think I don't know
what you're doing, Mara?
- I know what you're doing!
- Stop it!
Stop! You'll hurt yourself again!
I know why you're here with me!
I know why you're looking after me!
What are you saying? You'll hurt yourself!
You'll gain nothing from me, Mara!
Calm down, calm down!
Okay? Calm down.
Ana, come on.
Be careful.
Let me get that.
Ana.
Ana!
Why?
Why did you even try to do that, huh?
I don't know.
I just wanna die.
Ugh, you idiot.
Ana.
I didn't save you the first time
just for you to ruin your life.
Why would you destroy yourself?
You're the one who got cheated on!
You know who should pay for this?
Your husband's harlot of a side chick!
It should be her!
Come here. Listen to me.
Sit up.
Listen to me.
Do you remember
what I told you back then?
Protect your marriage with your life.
Because men...
easily get tempted!
So what you should do
is get rid of the temptation!
Ma?
Come on, Ana.
It's enough
that one of us made a mistake.
That one allowed another woman
to ruin one marriage.
Enough.
Okay?
Come here. Come here, baby.
Here. I bought dinner.
Because even a fool who's in love
needs to eat.
And now you're bawling your eyes out.
You were so brave earlier.
Beth, you were just supposed
to test his loyalty.
Why did you let it get that far?
Diane...
I'm not sure what I feel. It's like...
it's like I was run over...
without knowing where the car came from.
Uh-huh.
Hit-and-run.
You could've just said that.
What if I stab you with this?
Do you want me to?
So you could wake up.
Diane, you don't understand.
I really love Ben.
Ma?
Before the sun could even rise,
he's already there,
according to the maid.
And he said he's not going to leave
until you talk to him.
Ben! Ben!
Ma'am, you're not allowed to be here.
- I need to talk to him!
Please leave! You can't!
- Why?
Sir Ben is not here!
- I'll wait for him inside!
He's not here, ma'am!
- I'm going to get in trouble.
I'll wait inside!
- Ma'am! Ma'am, please leave!
I'll go wait inside.
- You can't be here!
Why did you let her in?
That's enough! Have you no shame?
I just need a minute.
He won't answer my calls!
It's only right to not answer you!
You homewrecker! Are you not ashamed?
April, close the gate!
He shouldn't talk to you!
- Just one minute!
No! You homewrecker!
- Close the gate, April!
Ma'am, please!
- Don't ever come back here!
Ben!
- Goodness me!
Ma'am, please open-- Ma'am!
Ma'am?
- Hmm?
- He's still there.
Okay.
Poor Ben...
Ma...
I'm just saying.
Ben, will you please leave?
I can't.
I need to talk to my wife.
Do you really think
she'll be able to talk to you?
Ben, you've hurt my daughter.
I'm-- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
But I don't have a mistress.
That Beth is not my mistress...
sir.
I can never do that to my wife because...
I love her so much.
I love Ana so much.
It's not right for you
to make a scene here.
I'm not making a scene here.
I'm just here for my wife.
I'm waiting because I want to talk to her.
Ben, please, let's talk.
We have nothing to talk about.
- Ben, I'm begging you--
- Go away.
I'm begging you, Ben. Ben.
You know he's still out there, right?
I didn't ask him to wait.
He didn't go home.
He didn't sleep or eat.
If the nanny hadn't begged him,
he would have gone without water.
He's crazy.
He's crazy for you.
Ma, it's not a compliment.
Fine.
You know, just talk to him. Okay?
Why?
Because you're not heartless, like me.
Talk to him.
If this goes on,
your husband might actually go crazy.
Come on.
I'm begging you. Let's talk.
No, no, no, Beth.
No, no, no.
- Just this once, please.
- No.
No, Beth. We have nothing to talk about.
- I'm begging you. Talk to me.
- Stop it, Beth.
Everything was fine until you came along.
Come on.
Why are you still waiting for Ana?
- Why?
- She doesn't--
- she doesn't want you anymore.
- What do you mean? Huh?
- Go away.
- You!
Ana, hold on.
You really can't help flirting
with my husband, huh?
You seriously followed Ben
here to my mom's house?
I wouldn't even be here
if only Ben had talked to me.
- Stop, Beth.
- Oh!
- Don't listen to her.
- You even had the guts
to demand that Ben talk to you.
Which Bible says you have
the right to someone else's spouse?
- Ana, let's go.
- Don't I have the right
- to speak?
- What?
What are you going to say?
All right, fine.
Beth, go.
- What?
- Go. Talk.
- Tell her
that we're not in a relationship.
And that kiss.
Tell her about that kiss!
That it was all on you. Come on!
- Reynaldo! Get out of my way!
- Imelda!
I can't let them
team up against Ana!
- Imelda--
- Stop it!
Your daughter isn't a child anymore.
Don't meddle in her battles.
Your daughter is in a fragile state!
If something bad happens to her--
I'll take care of it.
I'll kill whoever hurts her.
Coming from you? Really?
Are you trying to be funny?
You're a big joke!
- Oh, please! Get out of my way!
- Imelda! Imelda!
Stop it!
All I'm trying to say is,
don't you trust your daughter?
That she can deal with this herself?
Beth, please.
Beth, come on, tell her.
Yes.
Ben and I are not in a relationship.
Okay, let's go. Let's go...
But I know that he likes me.
What?
- Oh, my God.
- Ben, I know it.
I can feel it! I can see it!
The way you held me.
The way you looked at me in the car.
You always offered
to give me a ride, remember?
Beth... that means nothing.
You're nothing to me.
Ben, you asked me
to come to the wharf.
That message was for my wife.
I've told you that. Wrong send, remember?
Are you going crazy?
Are you going crazy thinking
I want to be alone with you there?
Me, crazy?
What about your wife?
Aren't you hurting yourself?
- Am I right? I know that.
- Oh, okay.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Okay, okay, okay.
So you think...
- you think you're a better woman than me?
- Come on, Ana.
That's why he likes you?
Ana...
Look at yourself.
You're not special.
- You're bland.
- Don't go there. Ana, let's go.
You're cheap.
Cheap? Really?
- Look who's talking.
- Ana, stop. Ana, Ana.
Between us,
who do you think acts more cheaply?
The one who hired a loyalty tester
or me, who your husband wants?
I get it! You're rich and pretty!
But you're so insecure!
Ana hired me to be a loyalty tester.
To find out if you were having an affair.
Listen to me, Ben.
She didn't just do it once.
She did the loyalty testing twice!
Once wasn't enough for her!
You have a mad wife! She hired me.
She hired me to test your loyalty again.
Listen to me!
Your wife doesn't want you anymore!
Your wife doesn't trust you!
Your wife doesn't love you!
Get out! Get out of my house!
- Get out!
- Ben!
Ben, please! Ben!
Ben!
What? What?
Loyalty testing.
That was unnecessary, Ana.
Ben, it started that night.
When you said you didn't leave,
but you lied.
So what did you want me to do?
I explained it to you.
The phone in your car.
Not mine.
I'm just saying, can you blame me?
I just want to say...
please trust me.
That's all.
Please trust me.
Because I'm not being unfaithful.
There are just so many things
about you that I don't get.
- What things?
- Small things.
And big things.
Things I don't understand.
Things that don't add up.
Then ask me.
I'll explain things to you.
Ana, you let this random person
in our lives.
In our life.
Okay?
And all of this happened
just because of loyalty testing.
I'm sorry.
Ana...
it's okay.
It's okay.
I love you.
Ana, it's okay.
It's okay.
Please, let's stop fighting.
Okay? Come here.
It's okay.
Will you be okay?
Yes.
You know, I think
you should talk to my doctor.
- Doctor?
- Yeah. My therapist.
You might need someone to talk to.
Ma, I...
A visit won't hurt.
Benjamin.
I'm very sorry.
I'm very, very sorry.
Thank you, Ma.
Take care.
Anyone home?
Hi, Auntie Beth!
Caloy is here.
Just leave him there. I'll look after him.
Come on, dear.
Let's go to Auntie Beth's room.
Stay there, okay?
H-Hello?
Hello, Ben!
Maybe we can talk now.
Ana isn't around, is she?
Hello?
Aren't you done yet?
What the hell, Diane?
You broke my phone!
Snap out of it, Betchay!
Stop bothering Attorney Ben.
I'll just tell him that I'm right.
That won't change his mind, Beth.
You were wrong from the very beginning.
You know what, I don't know
if you're a fool or just plain stupid.
Ben loves me.
He loves you?
Did you hear him say that?
Did he say, "Beth, I love you.
I'll leave my wife for you"?
Was it that clear?
He can't tell me,
because his damn wife
is always hanging around!
Beth!
No matter what you say,
that's what I felt.
Diane...
I've given my all my whole life,
you know that.
But Ben is the only one
I haven't given anything to.
Yet he's the only one
who made me feel I'm worthy...
to be saved, cared for, protected...
He did all that
without asking for anything in return.
Now tell me he doesn't love me.
Betchay, that's concern.
It's just concern, nothing more.
He showed you a little kindness,
and you think he's in love with you?
Have you lost your mind?
Diane, you don't get it.
You don't understand
because you haven't seen
the way he looks at me.
Diane, I'm not crazy.
I'm not losing my mind, Diane,
what I'm saying is true.
That's why I need Ben.
I can't have peace if I'm not with him.
Diane, please help me--
So?
Are you awake now, huh?
Are your eyes finally open?
I won't help you, Beth.
I'll only stand by you
if you stop this madness.
You're destroying yourself.
Caloy and I are leaving.
So, are you saying I'm not okay?
You look worried.
I understand.
But not being okay is not a failure.
It is information.
I-I just...
Do I have
the same condition as Mama?
Well, every case is different.
There are other factors
like environment, experiences,
coping habits, and other things.
I love my mother.
But I don't... I don't want to be like...
Look, Ana...
just focus on what matters now.
I'm going to prescribe you some meds.
But that alone will not fix things.
Therapy can help.
Get over here!
- Why is he there?
- Uh...
- Is he still alive?
- I don't know, ma'am.
Sorry, I fell asleep.
Don't ever do that again, okay?
I'm going to eat now.
I told the office
I'm taking the day off.
- Ben? No.
- Mm?
You're missing too much work lately.
Oh, that's not true.
I'm still answering calls and e-mails.
I have my phone.
You know what the best thing
about being a CEO is?
I can make other people do my job.
Hey, don't be
that kind of boss everyone hates.
I'm just kidding.
They know I want to spend time with you,
so I took the day off.
What?
But the doctor's appointment is over.
- We're going somewhere.
- Where?
Patience, my love.
- Ben?
- Get in.
Beth is so stupid. What was she thinking?
Do you really think
she'd talk about her nonsense?
Plus, a lot happened with my son and me.
Sweetie, sit down. Go play with your toys.
So, what's her plan now, anyway?
She says she loves and needs the attorney.
Wow, she's totally lost it!
I talked to her and literally slapped her,
but nothing changed.
So Caloy and I just left
because I really can't help her.
Then there's another problem
when you got home.
How was I to know that bastard
was already waiting at my house?
Oh, man, Bridge...
Ugh, I'm so tired.
I'm just so exhausted.
But look at your son,
he still has so much energy.
Hang in there, babe. Come on.
The time will come for us to win.
Just have faith. You got this.
Okay.
Do you remember this place?
This is where we said our vows.
What was that again?
You forgot already?
Ana... never.
For as long as I breathe...
and I love you more than my life.
Is it still the same?
Of course, Ana.
Always.
It will never change.
Let's go home?
Are we okay now?
We should be.
I made a mistake.
I trusted my gut feeling
more than I trusted my husband.
But you know my fears,
my pains growing up...
Yes, Ana, I know.
I just don't want to end up like Mama.
No. Never.
I'm sorry.
God knows I love you.
I love you too, Ana, so much. I love you.
But it still hurts.
What?
The kiss.
I know, I know.
Just let me be jealous for a while.
Okay.
Angel!
This is the only way we could think of...
to say goodbye to you.
Because we don't know where Eric took you.
But we hope these will reach you.
Cheers?
- Cheers.
No alcohol for you.
Caloy?
I understand
if you can't send Caloy to school.
But what about his therapy sessions?
Diane, you know the kid needs them.
Mike, I'm not neglecting Caloy.
I'm just looking for--
What? Another doctor to assess him?
Are you gonna make him adjust
to a new treatment plan?
Come on, Diane!
Mike, please.
Don't give me that attitude.
You shouldn't have kept my son
away from me.
Quit being selfish.
You keep demanding to spend time with him.
But have you really thought
about Caloy's well-being?
Do you think
you can give him what he needs?
Daddy! Daddy!
Are you and Ben okay now?
Yes.
No, I...
I guess so.
I want us to be okay.
That's why I went home with him.
But have you talked about...
...the loyalty testing?
Yes.
And...
he forgave me.
Right away?
Yes.
Well, of course...
he got mad.
He was offended and hurt.
But...
h-he said he understood
where I was coming from.
Maybe I should apologize to Ben too.
I was the one
who suggested the loyalty test.
No, Kat, it's not your fault.
You might've suggested it,
but I could've chosen not to do it.
In the end,
I decided to do that loyalty test.
Ana, is that her?
It's okay, Kat.
Set Ben free.
Has everything that happened
not sunk in yet?
I won't stop until--
Until you get my husband?
Tell me.
After you confronted me and Ben...
has he reached out to you?
Has he sent you a message?
Or checked up on you?
No?
And you still think my husband likes you?
He can't do any of that because of you.
He hasn't reached out to you
because he doesn't like you.
I'm the one Ben likes.
I'm the one he loves.
This conversation is going nowhere,
so please just stop.
But this is your fault.
You're the reason Ben and I met.
That's true.
I admit.
If it wasn't for the loyalty test,
you wouldn't have fallen for him.
But it's done.
He passed the test.
But your husband isn't loyal.
It was just one kiss that you started.
Ben has another woman!
You didn't know, did you?
He didn't tell you?
He met with a woman.
A beautiful woman.
You expect me to believe that?
Coming from you,
the woman who insists I leave my husband?
You and your delusions--
Are you finally awake?
You're the one who needs to wake up.
You can reach all you want,
but you will never ever touch what's mine.
The show's over.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- I'm leaving.
- I'm leaving. I must find Joel!
- Give me back the keys!
- Let me go! Let me go!
- You can't leave!
I need to find Joel!
At least let me find his body!
No, Regina! Give me back the keys!
Let me go!
Why won't you let me go?
Please let me go!
At least let me find Joel's body!
- Regina, you have to calm down.
- How? I need to find Joel!
- Unlock this door! I'm leaving!
- I said calm down!
Calm down.
- I want to see Joel...
- Calm down now.
I'm right here.
Okay...
Your father committed suicide.
This case is closed.
- Sir!
- Escort her out!
Sir, please help us. My father was killed.
Please believe me! I just need your help!
- Escort her out.
- Sir, please help us.
You're all useless! I'm not leaving
before I get justice for my father!
I'm sorry, miss.
Hey, did you follow
the guy I told you about?
Yes,
I'll send you a picture of his companion.
Thanks for your help.
Sorry for the trouble.
Please send it right away.
I'm not doing this again, okay?
Let your father's soul rest.
- Cheers!
- Come on, guys!
Guys! Come on, join us.
I think I know you.
Actually...
I know you too.
You know...
there's something we need to discuss.
Really?
Could I get on and take your time?
So...
what do you want to talk about?
Well...
- something that interests you.
- Hmm?
Attorney Ben.
All right.
Then we have a lot to talk about.
Excuse me.
A bottle of whiskey. Thanks.
What?
The heck? She did that?
Are you okay?
Yes.
That's not okay.
- I'll talk to that woman.
- No!
I don't want you anywhere near her.
I don't want her
to get even more delusional
and think that you like her.
Okay.
She also said you met with another woman
when you accompanied her
to the Overseas Welfare Desk.
Mary?
Mary used to work with me at the firm.
She worked there for like a year.
I saw her at the café
while buying souvenirs for you.
Souvenirs?
That is so silly.
Ana.
Do you believe me?
Yes.
I trust you more than her.
This... Oh, my God, Ana.
This! I love this.
Thank you.
I love you, stranger.
Good night.
Okay, good night.
Today marks a new chapter
for Azucarera de Saguil.
The Bagasse Energy Plant is not
just an ordinary investment.
It's an investment for the people
who will benefit from it
for decades to come.
So, thank you very much.
Cheers to all of you. Thank you.
Ben! Hey!
- Congratulations.
- Thank you, sir.
You keep proving
that choosing you
to lead the azucarera
- was indeed the right thing to do.
- Oh, Uncle...
The azucarera
wouldn't have gone this direction
if it weren't for you, Ben.
- So, congratulations.
- Thank you, Auntie. Thank you very much.
- Cheers.
- Cheers to you, sir.
- Cheers to that.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yeah. Nice to meet you too.
Please have fun, and thank you for coming.
- Thank you. Thank you so much. Yeah, yeah.
- Congratulations.
Thank you, thank you. Yeah, Joy?
Attorney,
someone is looking for you.
He's waiting in your office.
He says it's urgent.
- Urgent? Okay, sure.
- Yes, sir.
Thank you, man. Please enjoy.
- Ana?
- Yeah?
- Excuse me, Uncle, Auntie.
- Okay.
I have to go to the office.
It's something urgent.
- Okay.
- Is that okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I'll leave the party to you.
- Okay. You'll come back, right?
- Yeah.
Yeah, of course, of course.
I'll just attend to this. Uncle!
Uncle, Auntie, excuse me.
I just have to run to the office quickly.
- Okay. Okay.
- I'll be back. Okay.
- Good luck!
- Thank you!
Okay, Joy, uh...
You know what?
Just call me if they need me.
- All right, I'll call you.
- Yeah? Okay. Thank you, Joy.
Brian.
Congratulations, Attorney!
I mean... sorry, Mr. CEO. Wow!
What are you doing here?
I didn't know there was an event here.
You see, Ben, I'm here because...
Well, I guess you know.
I'm here to borrow money.
You want to borrow money?
Yeah, I'm short on money.
I don't know anyone else with money
besides you.
Why don't you join the celebration
and let's have a drink?
Ben, I'm here to talk to you.
Hmm.
Okay.
I'll get back to you.
Take a left.
Turn left, Mara.
My niece was at the café
where the confrontation happened.
She said the woman is younger.
- Really?
- And a loyalty tester.
What the hell is that?
I don't know either,
but I'll get back to you.
- I'll do some research first.
- Mm.
Research or snooping for hot gossip?
I guess the latter.
Hello, Ma? I'm...
Okay, okay.
Mister,
can you please not drive too close?
The people in the car in front of us
might get suspicious.
Who are we following?
Your husband?
Yes, I want to catch him
with his mistress.
Ben, don't be surprised, but...
- but I had to do this.
- Excuse me.
Wh--
Why did you tie her up?
- She was...
- Why?
She was hurting herself.
You shouldn't have tied her up.
Where are her meds?
It's all gone.
- Stay away from me.
- It's me, Ben. Ging.
- Ging?
- Ben, she might...
- It's me, Ben.
- No!
- She could hurt herself.
- Go away!
- No! Go away!
- I'll help you.
- I said go away!
- Stay away from me!
- Ging. Ging.
- Relax. I'll help you.
- Don't touch me!
- I'll help you. It's me, Ben.
- Go away! Leave!
- I'm untying you, okay?
- Stay away from me!
- Just relax.
- No!
- Don't touch me.
- Just calm down, okay? Relax.
- Stop resisting, Ging!
- No! Don't!
- Stay still.
- Go away! No!
See? I'm untying you.
- She's hurting herself.
- See? Look.
- You're free now.
- Ben.
Where's Joel's body?
- I don't know.
- You're lying!
You're wrong
about what you're thinking.
I don't know.
Joel left, and I don't know where he is.
- He left.
- That's not true!
He left without saying where he was going.
- He's gone.
- That's not true!
- You know where Joel is!
- Ging.
I don't know.
- You killed my husband!
- No!
You killed my husband!
- You killed my husband!
- Ging.
You killed my husband!
I knew it! You killed my husband!
Stop. That's enough.
- You killed my husband.
- Shh. Hush now.
You killed him.
Let me out of here!
I'm not an animal!
Hey! Let me out!
Let me out of here! I'm not an animal!
Let me out of here!
Can you hear me?
Yes! Help me, please!
Just a sec.
Please help me.
Miss, please help me.
I want to get out of here.
I'm begging you.
Please help me. I want to get out of here.
Please, I'm begging you.
Mr. CEO.
You're hiding something
from your wife again.
How much do you want?
Three million is nothing
compared to the life
you're protecting, Mr. CEO.
If you could hide something
that's not a big deal,
you're probably hiding
something even bigger.
Why would I have to redeem myself
if I didn't do anything wrong?
I'll fix it.
I'll call you.